University Advancement Division Records UA043
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Development research, 1984, 1999; UA043.003; 3.28 Linear Feet
  - Laury, John W. - Leh, David W. Jr., 1984 April 30; UA043.000421 (Box 12)
  - Lehan, Ralph E. - Levin, Mrs. Harold J. (Carol Strogoff), 1984 April 30; UA043.000422 (Box 12)
  - Levin, Dr. Harry - Lewis, Walter, 1984 May 3; UA043.000423 (Box 12)
  - Lewis, William - Linial, Maxine, 1984 May 3; UA043.000424 (Box 12)
  - Link, Gertrude - Logan, Alexander, 1984 May 3; UA043.000425 (Box 12)
  - Logan, Mrs. Alexander - Lubash, Barbara, 1984 May 3; UA043.000426 (Box 12)
  - Luber, Philip - Macdonald, Dr. Bernard, 1984 May 3; UA043.000427 (Box 12)
  - Macdonald, Bruce - Madison, William, 1984 May 3; UA043.000428 (Box 12)
  - Madsen, Robert - Mahoney, Dr. Stephen A. 3rd, 1984 May 3; UA043.000429 (Box 12)
  - Mahoney, Thomas, H. - Mann, Robert, 1984 May 3; UA043.000430 (Box 13)
  - Mann, Rona - Maron, Nancy, 1984 May 3; UA043.000431 (Box 13)
  - Maron, Dr. Theodore - Mason, Dr. Andrew, 1984 May 3; UA043.000432 (Box 12)
  - Mason, Calee - McAdam, Theresa, 1984 May 3; UA043.000433 (Box 12)
  - McAfee, Dr. Robert - McDermott, Mary, 1984 May 3; UA043.000434 (Box 12)
  - McDermott, Dr. Richard - McKenney, Peter, 1984 May 3; UA043.000435 (Box 12)
  - McKenney, Thomas - McSweeney, Edward, 1984 May 3; UA043.000436 (Box 12)
  - McSweeney, Edward - Merrifield, Mrs. Stephen, 1984 May 3; UA043.000437 (Box 12)
  - Merrill, Albert E. - Millen, Dr. David, 1984 May 8; UA043.000438 (Box 12)
  - Millen, Harry - Miner, Margaret L., 1984 May 8; UA043.000439 (Box 13)
  - Miner, Richard S. - Mond, Ms. Carla R., 1984 May 8; UA043.000440 (Box 12)
  - Mondello, Mrs. Patricia C. (Ms. Patricia F. Caffrey) - Morine, John P., 1984 May 8; UA043.000441 (Box 12)
  - Morine, William C. - Moxham, Douglas G., 1984 May 8; UA043.000442 (Box 12)
  - Moxham, Mrs. Douglas G. (Maren Gale) - Murray, Ms. Patricia A., 1984 May 8; UA043.000443 (Box 12)
  - Murray, Paul R. - Nathanson, Dr. Robert H., 1984 May 11; UA043.000444 (Box 12)
  - Nathanson, Robert M. - Newton, Edmund H., 1984 May 11; UA043.000445 (Box 12)
  - Newton, Mrs. G K Jr. (Cynthia G. Newton) - Nold, George W. Jr., 1984 May 11; UA043.000446 (Box 12)
  - Nolen, Dr. William A. - Obrien, Dr. James J.H., 1984 May 11; UA043.000447 (Box 12)
  - O'Brien, John A. - Oleson, Peter C., 1984 May 11; UA043.000448 (Box 12)
  - Oley, Robert B. - Osborne, Mrs. Helen W. (Helen A. Wachtel), 1984 May 11; UA043.000449 (Box 12)
  - Osborne, Mrs. Katherine - Paley, Steven, 1984 May 15; UA043.000450 (Box 12)
  - Paley, William - Parker, Mrs. Olean Rogers, 1984 May 15; UA043.000451 (Box 12)
  - Parker, Richard - Patterson, Dr. William, 1984 May 15; UA043.000452 (Box 12)
  - Pastor, M and M, Norm - Speing, M and M, JK, 1984 June 14; UA043.000453 (Box 12)
  - Patti, Charles - Penta, Dr. Walter, 1984 May 14; UA043.000454 (Box 12)
  - Pento, Tony - Petersen, Mrs. Alexander, 1984 May 14; UA043.000455 (Box 12)
  - Petersen, Andro - Piazza, James, 1984 May 14; UA043.000456 (Box 12)
  - Picard, Anne - Plich, David, 1984 May 14; UA043.000457 (Box 12)
  - Plimpton, Mrs. Henry - Porter, Mrs. James, 1984 May 14; UA043.000458 (Box 12)
  - Porter, John - Pretti, William, 1984 May 14; UA043.000459 (Box 12)
  - Previte, Dr. Steven - Quattlebaum, Poppy, 1984 May 14; UA043.000460 (Box 12)
  - Quattrone, Mrs. Katherine - Rapoport, Mrs. Joan, 1984 May 14; UA043.000461 (Box 12)
  - Rapoport, Morris - Reese, Thomas, 1984 May 14; UA043.000462 (Box 12)
  - Reese, Thomas - Ribeck, Nancy, 1984 May 15; UA043.000463 (Box 12)
  - Ribicoff, Sen Abraham - Riley, Dr. Steven, 1984 May 14; UA043.000464 (Box 12)
  - Riley, Dr. William - Roberts, Laurie, 1984 May 15; UA043.000465 (Box 12)
  - Roberts, Leslie J. - Rogers, Michael, 1984 May 21; UA043.000466 (Box 12)
  - Rogers, Myran Edward - Rosenberg, Paul B., 1984 May 21; UA043.000467 (Box 12)
  - Rosenberg, Mrs. Paul B. (Marcia Fershtman) - Rounds, Dr. Charles E., 1984 May 21; UA043.000468 (Box 12)
  - Rounds, Dr. Charles E. Jr. - Russell, Bruce E., 1984 May 21; UA043.000469 (Box 12)
  - Russell, Charles A. - Sak, Matthew F., 1984 May 21; UA043.000470 (Box 12)
  - Sakai, Toshitada - Santos, Dr. George P., 1984 May 25; UA043.000471 (Box 12)
  - Santos, Dr. John P. - Scheck, Dr. Raymond, 1984 May 25; UA043.000472 (Box 12)
  - Schecter, Mrs. Dorothy - Schulaner, Dr. Frederic A., 1984 May 25; UA043.000473 (Box 12)
  - Schuler, Jack W. - Sears, Helen J., 1984 May 25; UA043.000474 (Box 12)
  - Sears, Mrs. Isaiah (Ruth Griffin) - Shapiro, Dr. Joel J., 1984 May 25; UA043.000475 (Box 12)
  - Shapiro, Dr. Joseph J. - Sherman, Vernon H., 1984 May 25; UA043.000476 (Box 12)
  - Sherman, Dr. William - Siegal, Dr. Richard, 1984 May 25; UA043.000477 (Box 12)
  - Siegal, Richard - Skarda, Robert, 1984 May 25; UA043.000478 (Box 12)
  - Skarnes, Richard - Smith, Dr. Francis, 1984 May 25; UA043.000479 (Box 12)
  - Smith, Dr. Francis - Soderholm-Difatte, Bryan, 1984 May 28; UA043.000480 (Box 12)
  - Soderstrom, Rolf, E. - Spilman, Edra, 1984 May 25; UA043.000481 (Box 12)
  - Spilsbury, John - Stearns, Steven, 1984 May 25; UA043.000482 (Box 12)
  - Spring, M and M, JK - Zwerling, M and M, S, 1984 June 14; UA043.000483 (Box 12)
  - Stebbins, Mrs. Albert - Stewart, David, 1984 May 25; UA043.000484 (Box 12)
  - Stewart, Donald - Stone, James, 1984 May 25; UA043.000485 (Box 12)
  - Stone, Jeffrey H. - Sullivan, Edward H., 1984 May 31; UA043.000486 (Box 12)
  - Sullivan, Edward L. - Swett, Dr. Alton H., 1984 May 31; UA043.000487 (Box 12)
  - Swett. Mrs. David D. (Emily Bettencourt) - Taub, Dr. Herbert L., 1984 May 31; UA043.000488 (Box 12)
  - Taub, Michael F. - Thomas, Cynthia R., 1984 May 31; UA043.000489 (Box 12)
  - Thomas, Mrs. Donald (Ruth G. Stanford) - Todd, Dr. John J., 1984 May 31; UA043.000490 (Box 12)
  - Todd, Lewis Paul - Trefethen, John F. Jr., 1984 May 31; UA043.000491 (Box 12)
  - Trefry, Mrs. John T. Jr. (Grace G. Neal) - Uhlir, Arthur Jr., 1984 May 31; UA043.000492 (Box 12)
  - Uhly, Ms. Barbara L. - Vargish, Andrew, 1984 May 31; UA043.000493 (Box 12)
  - Vargus, Mrs. Ione D. (Ione Dugger) - Vokey, Wesley C., 1984 May 31; UA043.000494 (Box 12)
  - Volckers, Hon G. Esteues - Walsh, James H., 1984 June 4; UA043.000495 (Box 12)
  - Walsh, John A. - Waxman, Harold H., 1984 June 4; UA043.000496 (Box 12)
  - Waxman, Dr. Harvey N. - Weiss, Robert J., 1984 June 4; UA043.000497 (Box 12)
  - Weiss, Dr. Samuel - Weyler, Michael E., 1984 June 4; UA043.000498 (Box 12)
  - Weyler, Dr. Morton J. - Widmer, Katharine V., 1984 June 4; UA043.000499 (Box 12)
  - Widrick, Rev Eugene R. - Wills, Dr. Frank S G, 1984 June 4; UA043.000500 (Box 12)
  - Wills, Ms. Laurel M. - Wolff, Roby N S, 1984 June 4; UA043.000501 (Box 12)
  - Wolff, Dr. Sheldon - Wrightson, Theresa A., 1984 June 5; UA043.000502 (Box 12)
  - Wrigley, Diane Smith - Young, Dr. Harry N., 1984 June 5; UA043.000503 (Box 12)
  - Ziter, Dr. William - Zynsky, John, 1984 June 6; UA043.000504 (Box 12)
  - Development research storage disks, 1999 May 3; UA043.003.014 (Box 14)
    12 disks.
- Funded project records, 2006 -- 2009; UA043.004; 0.96 Linear Feet
  The funded project records document the fundraising and grant-funding initiatives done on behalf of the Jebsen Center for Counter Terrorism Studies at the Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy at Tufts University. These records were compiled by George Kosar, former Associate Director of Corporate and Foundation Relations at the Fletcher School, and primarily reflect his actions and those of Stacy Neal, former Associate Director of the Center for Emerging Market Enterprises at the Fletcher School. Records date from 2006 to 2009 and include grant applications and background documents, correspondence, event information, clippings, and funding strategy reports. Entities mentioned include the National Institute of Justice (NIJ), the Smith Richardson Foundation (SRF), the Personnel Security Research Center (PERSEREC), and the Lynde and Harry Bradley Foundation.
  This series contains restricted material. Restrictions related to specific material are listed in the detailed contents list.
  - NIJ Transnational Crime and Terror paperwork, 2007 January; UA043.004.011.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 8)
    20 years from date of creation.
  - Transnational crime Eastern Europe, circa 2007; UA043.004.011.00006; 2 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 9-10)
  - DOJ-COPS U.S. Muslims, 2007 July; UA043.004.011.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Room reservations, 2009; UA043.004.011.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - $300 deposits, 2009; UA043.004.011.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Housing, circa 2009; UA043.004.011.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Leases, 2009; UA043.004.011.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Staff goals and reviews, 2007; UA043.004.011.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Grant research subscription services, 2007; UA043.004.011.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Grant, gift, proposal models, circa 2005 -- 2007; UA043.004.011.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Africa Conference general, 2007 -- 2008; UA043.004.011.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Africa Conference panelist info, 2007 -- 2008; UA043.004.011.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Africa essay contest, 2008; UA043.004.011.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - TSWG intel in denied areas/NGO, 2007 -- 2008; UA043.004.011.00018; 2 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 22-23)
  - NIJ counter terrorism proposal, 2007; UA043.004.011.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - U.S. Muslims NIJ and SR, 2007; UA043.004.011.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Diasporas grant proposals and background research, circa 2006; UA043.004.011.00021; 2 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 26-27)
  - Perserec report, 2007; UA043.004.011.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Perserec contract, 2007; UA043.004.011.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Smith Richardson grant proposal and background research, 2006; UA043.004.011.00024; 2 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 30-31)
  - Luce Foundation collab grant, 2007; UA043.004.011.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - NSF (Preserec PH 2), 2007; UA043.004.011.00026; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Preserec proposal, 2006 -- 2007; UA043.004.011.00027; 2 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 34-35)
  - Bradley miscellaneous correspondence, 2007; UA043.004.011.00028; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Bradley Opportunity Fund, 2007; UA043.004.011.00029; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Bradley Foundation grant, 2006; UA043.004.011.00030; 2 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 38-39)
- Fundraising materials, 1930 -- 2014; 1980 -- 2014; UA043.005; 4.92 Linear Feet
  This series contains materials related to fundraising for Tufts, including planning materials, reports, gift planning brochures, and promotional materials. This series also includes some marketing materials relating to specific events such as invitations and fliers. The types of material in this series overlaps with Special events records and communications and marketing materials. Fundraising materials, however, tend to be broader in scope than Special events records and concerned with both promotional and internal material. Materials date circa 1930-2014, with the majority dating 1980-2014.
  Materials in this series are arranged chronologically.
  - Development fundraising brochures, circa 1930 -- 1991; UA043.005.007.00017; 3 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 17-19)
  - 1953, UA043.005.015.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - 1956, UA043.005.015.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - 1959, UA043.005.015.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - circa 1960s, UA043.005.SB147.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box Shared 147, Folder 1)
  - 1970, UA043.005.015.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - 1977, UA043.005.015.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Packard Society, circa 1978--1990s; UA043.005.015.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - 1979, UA043.005.015.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - circa 1980s, UA043.005.015.00008; 2 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 8-9)
  - 1980, UA043.005.015.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - 1981, UA043.005.015.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - The Tufts Report publications, 1981 -- 1983; UA043.005.SB147.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box Shared 147, Folder 2)
  - 1983, UA043.005.015.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - 1985, UA043.005.015.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - 1986, UA043.005.015.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - 1987, UA043.005.015.00014; 2 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 15-16)
  - The New Campaign publications, 1987 -- 1988; UA043.005.SB147.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box Shared 147, Folder 3)
  - 1988, UA043.005.015.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - circa 1990s, UA043.005.015.00016; 2 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 18-19)
  - 1991, UA043.005.015.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - 1992, UA043.005.015.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Tufts Report on Annual Giving, 1992 -- 1993; UA043.005.SB147.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box Shared 147, Folder 4)
  - 1993, UA043.005.015.00019; 2 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 22-23)
  - Development, 1933; UA043.005.015.00020; 2 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 24-25)
  - 1994, UA043.005.015.00021; 2 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 26-27)
  - 1995, UA043.005.015.00022; 2 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 28-29)
  - 1996, UA043.005.015.00023; 2 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 30-31)
  - 1997, UA043.005.015.00024; 2 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 32-33)
  - 1998, UA043.005.015.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - 2001, UA043.005.015.00026; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - 2002, UA043.005.015.00027; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - 2003, UA043.005.015.00028; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - The President's Luncheon, 2004; UA043.005.015.00029; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - 2006, UA043.005.015.00030; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Parents Weekend, 2007; UA043.005.015.00031; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Office of Special Events, 2007; UA043.005.015.00032; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - 2011, UA043.005.015.00033; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - 2013, UA043.005.015.00034; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Beyond Boundaries publication, circa 2006 -- 2008; UA043.005.016.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Tufts Blueprint and Beyond Boundaries publications, circa 2008 -- 2013; UA043.005.016.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Tufts Blueprint and Beyond Boundaries publications, 2008 -- 2014; UA043.005.016.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Tufts Blueprint publication, 2011 -- 2013; UA043.005.016.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Special events records, 2007 -- 2013; UA043.006; 2.66 Linear Feet; 4 Digital Object(s)
  This series contains marketing material related to university events, including fliers, invitations, and occasionally event programs. The types of material in this series overlaps with Fundraising materials and Communications and marketing materials. Special events records, however, tend to be more narrowly focused on the advertisement of events rather than general or targeted fundraising. Materials date from 2007-2013.
  Materials in this series preserve their received arrangement and are organized chronologically.
  - International Parents Reception, 2007 August 27; UA043.006.016.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Charles Tufts Society faculty and staff luncheon, 2007 September 28; UA043.006.016.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - School of Medicine campus visit, 2007 October 4 -- 6; UA043.006.016.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Athletic Awards Ceremony, 2007 October 5; UA043.006.016.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Parents Weekend, 2007 October 12 -- 14; UA043.006.016.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Boillot Reception, 2007 October 30; UA043.006.016.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Athletics Campaign Launch, 2007 December 12; UA043.006.016.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering Campus Visit, 2008 April 3 -- 5; UA043.006.016.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Granoff Music Center One Year Anniversary, 2008 February 9; UA043.006.016.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Edward R. Murrow Forum on Issues in Journalism, 2008 April 14; UA043.006.016.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Neubauer Recognition Dinner, 2008 April 14; UA043.006.016.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Hillel end of campaign celebration, 2008 May 1; UA043.006.016.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - School of Dental Medicine skybreaking ceremony, 2008 May 2; UA043.006.016.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Charles Tufts Society and Scholarship Donors Luncheon, 2008 May 15; UA043.006.016.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Tufts Night at Pops, 2008 May 15; UA043.006.016.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Packard Society Reception, 2008 May 16; UA043.006.016.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - President's Reception, 2008 May 17; UA043.006.016.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Bendetson Hall Reception, 2008 May 17; UA043.006.016.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Mid-campaign celebration New York City, 2008 June 5; UA043.006.016.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Arts and Sciences Reception, 2008 July 31; UA043.006.016.00024; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - International Parents Reception, 2008 August 25; UA043.006.016.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Dental School Campus Visit, 2008 September 4 -- 5; UA043.006.016.00026; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Tufts financial network event, 2008 September 10; UA043.006.016.00027; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Charles Tufts Society Faculty and Staff Lunch, 2008 September 18; UA043.006.016.00028; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Endowed Professorship Dinner, 2008 September 22; UA043.006.016.00029; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Varis Campus Center Opening, 2008 September 23; UA043.006.016.00030; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Bergstrom Recognition Dinner, 2008 September 23; UA043.006.016.00031; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Medical School campus visit, 2008 October 2 -- 4; UA043.006.016.00032; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Fletcher 75th Anniversary, 2008 October 11; UA043.006.016.00033; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Parents Weekend, 2008 October 17 - 19; UA043.006.016.00034; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Los Angeles Athletic Event, 2008 November 10; UA043.006.016.00035; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - San Francisco Athletic Event, 2008 November 11; UA043.006.016.00036; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Annual Fund Leadership Dinner, 2008 December 10; UA043.006.016.00037; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Tufts Financial Network Speaker Series, 2009 January 29; UA043.006.016.00038; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - 2nd Anniversary Granoff Music Center, 2009 January 31; UA043.006.016.00039; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Fares Lecture, 2009 February 2; UA043.006.016.00040; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Fares Lecture CDs, 2009 February 2; UA043.006.016.00041; 1 Folder(s); 2 Digital Object(s) (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Grisard Professorship Dinner, 2009 February 4; UA043.006.016.00042; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Campus Visit, 2009 March 5 -- 7; UA043.006.016.00043; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Richard E. Snyder Presidential Lecture and Dinner featuring Michael Pollan, 2009 March 24; UA043.006.016.00044; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - Charles Francis Adams Lecture featuring Martin Broughton, 2009 March 23; UA043.006.016.00045; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - Real Estate Luncheon, 2009 April 3; UA043.006.016.00046; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - Dedication of Alex's Place, 2009 April 26; UA043.006.016.00047; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - Tufts Night at Pops, 2009 May 14; UA043.006.016.00048; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - Charles Tufts Society and Scholarship Donors Lunch, 2009 May 14; UA043.006.016.00049; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 49)
  - Packard Society Reception, 2009 May 15; UA043.006.016.00050; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 50)
  - President's Reception, 2009 May 16; UA043.006.016.00051; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 51)
  - Agnes Varis Campus Center Auditorium Celebration, 2009 June 10; UA043.006.016.00052; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 52)
  - Tufts Financial Network Speaker Series, 2009 June 16; UA043.006.016.00053; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 53)
  - International Parents Reception, 2009 August 31; UA043.006.016.00054; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 54)
  - Cummings School Horse Isolation Unit Event, 2009 September 8; UA043.006.016.00055; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 55)
  - Friedman School Campus Visit, 2009 September 10; UA043.006.016.00056; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 56)
  - Endowed Professorship Dinner, 2009 September 15; UA043.006.016.00057; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 57)
  - Charles Tufts Society Faculty and Staff Breakfast, 2009 September 17; UA043.006.016.00058; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 58)
  - Snyder Presidential Lecture, 2009 October 1; UA043.006.016.00059; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 59)
  - The Curio House Reception and Tour, 2009 October 16; UA043.006.016.00060; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 60)
  - Parents Weekend, 2009 October 16 -- 18; UA043.006.016.00061; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 61)
  - Dental School VEI Opening Celebration, 2009 November 20; UA043.006.016.00062; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 62)
  - Annual Fund Leadership Dinner, 2009 December 8; UA043.006.016.00063; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 63)
  - Tufts Financial Network, 2009 December 10; UA043.006.016.00064; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 64)
  - Granoff Music Center Presentation, 2010 January 30; UA043.006.016.00065; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 65)
  - Schmidheiny Recognition Dinner, 2010 February 7; UA043.006.016.00066; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 66)
  - Tufts Financial Network Speaker Series CEO, 2010 April 5; UA043.006.016.00067; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 67)
  - Athletics Campus Visit, 2010 April 8 -- 10; UA043.006.016.00068; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 68)
  - Haber Professorship, 2010 April 22; UA043.006.016.00069; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 69)
  - Snyder Presidential Lecture, 2010 April 26; UA043.006.016.00070; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 70)
  - Real Estate Luncheon, 2010 May 7; UA043.006.016.00071; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 71)
  - Neuroscience Ambassadors Day, 2010 May 12; UA043.006.016.00072; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 72)
  - Charles Tufts Society and Scholarship Donor Luncheon, 2010 May 20; UA043.006.016.00073; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 73)
  - Tufts Night at Pops, 2010 May 20; UA043.006.016.00074; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 74)
  - Packard Society and Trustee Reception, 2010 May 21; UA043.006.016.00075; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 75)
  - Steeplechase Pit Dedication, 2010 May 22; UA043.006.016.00076; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 76)
  - Class of 2010 Student and Parents Reception, 2010 May 22; UA043.006.016.00077; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 77)
  - Tufts Financial Lecture, 2010 May 26; UA043.006.016.00078; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 78)
  - Fares Lecture Programs, 1994 -- 1998; UA043.006.016.00079; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 79)
  - Charles Tufts Society Faculty and Staff Breakfast, 2010 September 16; UA043.006.016.00080; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 80)
  - Investment in Faculty Dinner, 2010 September 22; UA043.006.016.00081; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 81)
  - Tufts Financial Network Wall Street Crash Course, 2010 October 15 -- 16; UA043.006.016.00082; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 82)
  - Hillel Dinner and Lecture, 2010 October 19; UA043.006.016.00083; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 83)
  - Parents Weekend, 2010 October 24; UA043.006.016.00084; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 84)
  - Merrin Dinner, 2010 October 26; UA043.006.016.00085; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 85)
  - Snyder Lecture, 2010 November 3; UA043.006.016.00086; 1 Folder(s) (Box 16, Folder 86)